infinitiusa.com 2009-06-06

# Infiniti Privacy & Legal - Infiniti USA

INFINITI Division of Nissan North America, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Nissan North America, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site (except that our affiliate, Infiniti Financial Services, owns information collected from credit pre-approval applications). We will not sell or rent this information to others. We will only share this information with our affiliates and retailers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment).

If you provide your Social Security Number to us, we will (1) protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers, (2) prohibit unlawful disclosure of Social Security numbers, and (3) limit access to Social Security numbers.

Infiniti uses two types of user information: anonymous information gathered from cookies and log files, and personal information you provide us for certain services. See below for definitions of each of these methods.

(Effective October 1, 2008)

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personal information, until a user provides that information (see below). If a user rejects or deletes the cookie, he/she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to receive notification of special offers, or participate in any contests that may take place. Cookies also enable us to track and aggregate clickstream behavior data. By doing this we can better target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site.

Infiniti also maintains standard web logs that record data about all visitors to this Web site. These logs may contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access this site.
  * Your IP address. (Your computer is automatically assigned an IP address when you surf the Internet.  
Your IP address is either static or dynamic. A static IP address may be identifiable to you; a dynamic  
address is usually not identifiable to you.)
  * The type of browser and operating system you use.
  * The date and time you visited this site.
  * The pages you viewed on this site.
  * The address of the Web site from which you linked.

Infiniti uses Web log and clickstream information to help us design our site, to identify popular site features and to make the site more useful for visitors. Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we normally do not attempt to identify individuals from these logs. However, we may use Web logs to identify persons attempting to break into, disrupt, or damage our site. We may share web log information with law enforcement personnel if we believe evidence exists, or is likely to occur, of a violation of federal, state or local laws or regulations.

Infiniti advertising at other non-Infiniti sites may be serviced by Infiniti service providers, who may use cookies to collect information about your visits to those sites. Information collected may include the pages visited, date and time, browser information and/or IP address. We normally make no attempt to link this information to you personally, except under circumstances described above. This information is gathered in order to help us customize and target our advertising to the needs and interests of our customers. If you wish to opt out of this tracking at our advertising at third party sites, please visit the following sites:

Users may choose to volunteer personal information (name, e-mail, address, phone number, etc.) in order for us to provide them with services such as brochure and information requests, surveys and contests, site announcements, and special offers at the time of the request or in the future.

If you previously gave us your e-mail address and no longer wish to receive e-mail announcements, you can have your name removed from our e-mail list by sending an e-mail to [unsubscribeUSA@Infiniti.com](mailto:unsubscribeUSA@Infiniti.com), calling, or by sending regular mail (see contact information below). Infiniti does not sell or rent user information to any third parties. We share user information with our affiliates and retailers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment). When the user signs up for certain services and offers on our site, we will share names or other contact information necessary for any associate third party to provide these services. Infiniti will share user information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected.

If a user's personal information changes, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by e-mailing [privacyUSA@Infiniti.com](mailto:privacyUSA@Infiniti.com) or by contacting Infiniti Consumer Affairs as outlined below.

If a user elects to e-mail a friend from this Web site, a function available from the "Build Your Vehicle" page, we ask for the friend's e-mail address. Nissan North America, Inc. captures this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.

Infiniti takes all reasonable precautions to protect our users' information, both while the information is being transmitted and after it is received by us.

When our credit pre-approval form asks users to enter sensitive information such as social security number, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL 128-bit encryption software, an industry standard for reputable organizations. While on a secure page, such as our credit pre-approval application form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing." For more information on the Infiniti Financial Services (IFS) privacy notice, see "IFS Privacy Policy" below.

Furthermore, once the information has been received by us, we use security procedures and policies commensurate with industry standards to safeguard against loss, theft, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure. If you have any questions about the security of our Web site, you can send an e-mail to [privacyUSA@Infiniti.com](mailto:privacyUSA@Infiniti.com).

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Infiniti is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

We retain the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will post those changes to this page so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use, share, and disclose all information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was collected.

Infiniti may disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, to any person performing audit, legal, services for Infiniti or Nissan North America, Inc.

Whenever possible, we will require any recipient of personal information for these purposes to agree in writing to hold the information in confidence, to use the information only for the permitted purpose, and to return or destroy the information when the services are completed. We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when required to do so by subpoena, court order, or warrant. Whenever feasible, Infiniti will notify the affected user by e-mail that such disclosure will or has occurred.

We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when we reasonably deem it necessary to protect the safety of (i) an individual, (ii) the public, or (iii) the security and reliability of Infiniti and/or this Web site.

Infiniti does not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to participate in any services offered on our Web site that require the submission of user information. If we learn that a user is under 13 and has submitted user information to us, we will delete that information as promptly as possible.

To contact Infiniti, click on the "Contact Us" link below or send mail to:  
Infiniti Consumer Affairs  
Attn: InfinitiUSA.com Privacy  
P.O. Box 685003  
Franklin TN 37068-5003  
Or, during business hours, call 1-800-662-6200.

Infiniti Financial Services (IFS), a division of Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation (NMAC), maintains its own privacy policy, in addition to Nissan North America, Inc.'s Web privacy policy. IFS's policy applies to the portions of the site where consumer credit pre-approval information is collected and to IFS consumers. IFS's privacy policy is as follows:

(Effective September 30, 2004)

This notice is for customers of: Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation; its division Infiniti Financial Services; and Nissan-Infiniti LT and Subaru Acceptance Corporation, for whom NMAC and IFS act as Servicer. This notice is given on behalf of both the owner and the servicer, if any, of your lease or contract.

We collect nonpublic personal information about you ("Private Information") from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on credit applications or other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and 
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies (credit bureaus).

Except as permitted by law, we do not disclose to third parties information we obtain from you or others for evaluation of your request for credit, including information: from credit applications; from consumer credit reports; from verification of your application information; and from credit and employment references. Otherwise, we may disclose Private Information about you, as a present or former customer, to: 

  * Companies that perform marketing services on our behalf; 
  * Other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements, including motor vehicle retailers, except where prohibited by state law; 
  * Companies, including motor vehicle retailers, with whom and through whom we offer you incentive, discount or bonus programs, to the extent permitted by state law; 
  * Our affiliates, including our motor vehicle manufacturing, distribution, services and sales affiliates, except where prohibited by law; and 
  * Non-affiliated third parties only as permitted by law.

Except as stated above, we do not share any Private Information with third parties. We restrict access to your Private Information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard all Private Information.

To view the Microsoft Privacy Statement and Terms of Use, [click here](http://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/fullnotice.aspx).
